http://www.smartsilver.com/privacy

Home
Textile & Fiber (regulated by US EPA)
SmartSilver
»
Privacy Statement of smartsilver.com
Info
Privacy Statement of smartsilver.com
F Group nano considers the responsible use of personal information to be a critical element in enabling the Internet to reach its potential as a serious tool for personal and professional activities. As the Internet changes our lives in a number of ways, F Group Nano is committed to respecting your privacy.
In general, you can visit www.smartsilver.com without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. There are times, however, when we may need information from you, such as your name, home or business address, and e-mail address. F Group Nano  will seek to let you know before we collect any personal information from you over the Internet. An example of when we may need personal information is if you use feedback or contact forms. When you choose to give us personal information over the Internet that we may request, F Group Nano will endeavor to let you know how we will use this information. F Group Nano will also seek to take appropriate steps to protect the information you share with us. When F Group Nano receives information about your session or about you, we may use it for research or to improve our site and the services we offer you. On www.smartsilver.com, IP addresses (the Internet address of a computer) are, in general, logged to track a user's session while the user remains anonymous. We analyze this data for certain trends and statistics, such as which parts of our site users are visiting and how long they spend there. In general, we do not link your IP addresses to anything personally identifiable to you. Some Smartsilver web pages use "cookies," which are small files that may be placed on your hard disk for record-keeping purposes. A cookie helps us remember who you are. Cookies can make your subsequent visits to the web page simpler and more seamless. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. (However, by not accepting cookies, some web pages may not display properly or you may not be permitted to access certain information.) F Group Nano encourages parents to take an active role in their children's use of the Internet and to spend time online with their children. Children may ask their parents to submit a request for information on their behalf. F Group Nano reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time by simply posting a changed Privacy Policy on this web site. The date of the most recent revision is provided below. The user is responsible for periodically checking the Privacy Policy for any changes when using this web site.If you have any questions or comments about our privacy practices, or would like to correct or update information provided to F Group Nano via its Web site, please contact us by sending an e-mail to info@fgroupnano.comREVISED December 18, 2018
Document Actions
Send this
Print this
©
2020
F Group Nano
Terms of Use —
Privacy Statement —
